GYEONGSEONG CREATURE 2
I was… a very special child.
It is okay to kill.
But always make sure… you're never caught.
Why never get caught?
A good son answers
his mother with a "yes."
He doesn't need to ask why.
That is not good manners,
dearest Seung-jo.
Yes.
Yes, Mother.
I just wanted
my mother's approval.
I wanted someone to comfort me.
Even if it was just one time.
Although we can't determine exactly
why only he can partially transform,
we can formulate a hypothesis.
What would that be?
Well, unlike all the other specimens
we've had so far,
Seung-jo inherited his Najin
from his biological mother.
As in
Akiko?
When he was a fetus
inside his mother's body,
the Najin altered
his genetic makeup altogether.
So we can conclude that the Najin
has evolved and mutated
in ways that no one could have predicted.
Like how Seishin…
manipulated her own body
so that she could offer
protection to her daughter.
You're saying the Najin has
kept the maternal instincts
of his mother Akiko.
That is what I believe.
How very interesting.
That's when I realized
that I was not a special person.
I was only
an experiment.
Did your meeting
with Master Jang go well today?
Yes.
The meeting went well.
Then it is time
to put all of your focus
on the next plan of ours,
dear Seung-jo.
You feeling okay?
How'd you sleep?
What's wrong?
Are you in pain?
Am I dreaming?
If so, I hope I never wake.
How I've missed you.
I've missed you so much
that no matter how many times
I would say it to myself…
it was still never enough.
What happened? Where's number 71?
We haven't found him yet.
It was you, wasn't it?
What are you planning here exactly?
I set him free.
That's all.
You know very well that letting him go
would only create chaos and wreak havoc.
Well, it's still…
more interesting
than the plan you're betting on.
And what plan is that?
I don't have to say.
Just know I know what it is.
I'm so hungry.
Goodness, he's toppling over.
How much did this guy have to drink?
Excuse me, sir.
I'm so hungry.
Something's come up.
GYEONGSEONG CREATURE
BETWEEN LIFE AND DEATH
EPISODE 6
BAIT
Did you give the order
to go after Master Jang?
Oh boy,
that's not what happened, all right?
You're in charge of the detectives,
are you not, Captain?
That means that it was you.
I had no choice.
I got six murder cases piling up on me.
With Ho-jae leaving evidence
all over the crime scene, it's suspicious.
How dare you pursue Master Jang.
The House of Golden Treasure
did so much for your family.
The reason you're sitting there is because
of what he did for your grandparents.
You call this justice? You are all
going after the wrong person here.
I need your help with something.
What?
My grandson has…
He has gone missing.
He's missing?
He went into a new hires training camp,
and then he received ten million won,
and now he won't answer when I call.
I called his work, and they said
there wasn't a training camp there at all.
Which company was it?
It's called Jeonseung.
SEONG JUN-MO (41 YEARS OLD)
RESEARCHER AT JEONSEUNG BIOTECH
OH KI-HOON (29 YEARS OLD)
BODYGUARD AT JEONSEUNG BIOTECH
AHN JONG-HYEOK
HIRED A MONTH AGO BY JEONSEUNG BIOTECH
The common denominator is
Jeonseung Biotech.
Should I dig into it?
You scared me.
Don't sneak up on me like that.
A question.
Did you meet the lady from yesterday?
How do you know each other?
She seemed pretty close
to Jang Ho-jae too.
- Detective Park, let's eat.
- Should I order from Grandma's Gukbap?
Want something?
It's all strange
and has been from the get-go.
I'm sure Jang Ho-jae
is super competent and all that,
but ordering him to go find evidence
about the suspect like it was nothing?
And then having me follow him,
and then you were…
you were at the ICU to keep an eye
on Mr. Kwon all night. Why is that?
You want food or what?
So all you guys have known each other
for a while now.
I'll order yours, then.
Huh?
Yes, this is Captain Yuh,
Violent Crimes Unit.
Huh?
Um, Captain?
An indiscriminate act
of murder occurred
on a subway station platform in Seoul.
Three civilians died,
and one victim was rushed
to the emergency room
after falling into critical condition.
An emergency report was sent out around
5:00 a.m. saying a man in his twenties…
According
to eyewitness accounts,
the suspect attacked…
- It can't be…
- …his first victim of three,
a transportation department employee who
was preparing for the day's operations.
I know that guy.
- After the first attack…
- He was a test subject at Jeonseung.
…the platform to attack…
Is that true?
Yeah.
He escaped this morning from his cell.
Another male in his forties
has reportedly been rushed…
I did it.
…receiving urgent treatment.
I was the one who let him go.
…the suspect was arrested
by the police while…
Why would you do something like that?
According to the police,
the motive of the crime…
To show the world.
They'll begin investigations…
If you want people to believe something,
you have to let them see it
with their own eyes.
Otherwise, it's just rumors.
Three people died because of you.
And even more people
could die very soon, all right?
Get it?
What do you mean by that?
What do you mean
that even more people could die very soon?
All I know is…
…Lady Maeda is up to no good.
I don't know the details,
but it's dangerous.
ASSAILANT ATTACKS
STATION EMPLOYEE INDISCRIMINATELY
CHAOS STRIKES MORNING COMMUTE
6 VICTIMS
How dangerous?
You know her better
than I do, but
we both know she'll stop at nothing.
It's true.
And would this situation
be part of her scheme?
To hopefully lure both of us
with him as bait?
So I'm guessing you still don't like me.
I don't know or trust you.
If it weren't for me,
you would never have gotten out.
I clearly remember you
stabbing me in the stomach once.
He's so strong.
He sent ten men flying across the room
when we tried to grapple him down.
He's as strong as a bull.
I had no choice but to taser the kid,
so I zapped him with my gun.
Only then did he collapse.
Look at him. Just look at him.
You call that a person?
Jong-hyeok.
Hey, look at me. Ahn Jong-hyeok.
What's wrong with you, huh?
- What the…
- Captain, are you okay?
You all right, sir?
I'll bring over the first aid kit for you.
Do you know each other?
BUGANG COMPANY
Yes, hello?
It's me, Captain Yuh.
Hey, you! Where are you right now?
I'm still alive. Don't worry.
So you're… back to this number again?
And
I remember.
Oh.
Okay.
How about you fill me in
on what's going on?
It's Jong-hyeok.
The Sinseol-dong lady's grandson.
He was the suspect.
He was recently hired at Jeonseung.
Mm.
Biotech.
What the hell are you doing?
You have no control
over your test subjects.
The press is out there going
completely nuts over your mess.
This was Seung-jo's doing, Chairman.
And why would he do that?
How about you ask
Lady Maeda that instead, sir?
Are you saying Maeda is the one
responsible for all this?
This is exactly why I warned you, Ji-oh.
If you recall, I warned you
that Lady Maeda's plan would sink
if you allowed her
to bring back Jang Tae-sang.
Because of her foolishness, everyone here
at the company is compromised.
If this reaches the public,
Jeonseung Biotech
may not live to see another day.
When your father
was the chairman of the company,
he inserted the Najin in my head
with the sole intention
that I continue devoting myself
to protecting Jeonseung
as well as his work.
If this whole fiasco continues to threaten
the welfare of your father's company,
then know I will absolutely eliminate
any threat without mercy,
whether that's Jang Tae-sang,
your incompetence, or even…
Lady Maeda. Do you understand?
Don't you forget.
All right.
First, let's clean up this mess.
Number 71 needs to be retrieved.
After that, we can talk with Lady Maeda.
Sound good?
What are you doing?
Were you planning on going alone?
Yeah, that's right.
There's no way you're going
with those injuries.
You haven't fully recovered.
You see that?
So let's go together since I'm healed.
- Still a no.
- Master Jang.
You're not going.
I don't wanna see you
getting hurt anymore.
If you go with me,
I won't be able to focus on the job.
The last thing I want is for you
to be in danger all over again.
I won't let that happen.
It's the 21st century.
Are you proposing
that whole old-fashioned thing
where your role
is to protect the lady right now?
Yes, I am.
I know I don't look it, but I'm, like,
over a hundred years old by now.
And I still have
an old-fashioned outlook on things.
I think it is a man's job
to make sure he protects his woman.
And I think
I'm a better fighter than you are.
Mm… It's still a no.
I'll have you know…
I do not die.
Also,
as your woman,
I wanna do everything together.
And not as someone
you have to always protect.
From now on…
I think we should just stick together.
Hmm?
You can't smile like that. It's cheating.
Well, so, smile for me one more time.
Uh-huh.
Who are they? What's going on?
Captain Yuh,
Jeonseung Biotech is waiting for you.
Are you crazy?
Where do you think you're going?
- To the station.
- And why the heck would you do that?
I know the kid.
Okay, so what?
He's been arrested.
There's nothing you can do.
Jeonseung won't let him stay in custody.
They're gonna try and handle
the situation one of two ways.
He'll either get taken back or get killed.
If I don't take action,
then he will never see his grandma again.
You never quit.
When will you learn?
You get beaten, attacked, tossed around,
and you barely survive it all.
You can't win against them, so why fight?
It's time you quit all this.
This is a battle you can't win, Ho-jae.
- Seung-jo.
- Go live your life instead!
Run away with her. I don't care.
Get ahead for once
while you still can. Huh?
Seung-jo, I do wanna live my life.
I wanna have a happy one with her.
I won't get that by running away.
If we have to keep running,
that's not a life worth living.
So I have to do this.
Yes, who's this?
It's Detective Noh.
Jeonseung Biotech
is trying to confiscate our guy.
Their people are here already.
Absolutely not.
You come in here out of nowhere
and expect us to hand over the suspect?
Well, the suspect has been infected.
Infected with?
I can't disclose that. It's classified.
Your Violent Crimes Unit
inquired about this recently?
Yes. And we haven't heard back
from Jeonseung Bio at all.
This portable metal canister
is specifically used
for precautionary measures. That's all.
The nitrogen gas suppresses aggression.
It seems people who are infected
can really act out.
The KDCA has sent out an official notice.
The National Police Agency
has approved the transfer.
So please transfer
the infected prisoner to us.
What exactly do you take the police for?
This guy is a suspect
in a serial murder case.
That's six victims in two months.
And also,
today, there were three victims
he attacked in the station.
You all come in here waving this thing,
thinking you can just take him away.
Guaranteeing the public's safety
is more important than your investigation,
don't you agree?
If an outbreak were
to spread uncontrollably,
who'll be responsible?
Will it be you, Captain?
Jeonseung Biotech is already there.
Well, then you're too late.
The station's only ten minutes away.
We still got time.
So what's your plan?
What are you gonna do?
Do what I do best.
Wreak havoc.
All right, I'm ready. Let's go.
I'll go too.
We should stick together.
Little fast, don't you think?
The speed limit's 50 kilometers.
Who cares?
I never paid much attention to that.
Does it check out?
Yes.
So I spoke with Disease Control,
and everything checks out.
Apparently, around the country,
a handful of people
are displaying symptoms
similar to the suspect in custody.
In order to prevent a widespread outbreak,
it's being treated with tight security.
And Jeonseung Biotech is currently
researching the origin of the outbreak.
Captain, why are they
covering the cameras up?
Ah shit.
Should I release the nitrogen gas?
Don't bother. Just open the door.
CAPTAIN YUH MYUNG-JUN
Yes, Captain.
Hey. Where are you?
Hey, I asked where you were.
Sir, I'm pursuing the Jeonseung Bio van.
- What?
- Listen, I'm sorry.
But something here still seems off,
and I know that we're done
with the investigation
'cause the killer was supposedly caught.
And I'm aware
that you don't think I'm reliable, but
I really need
to follow my instinct this time, Captain.
So I'm sorry.
You're working for once.
Just don't lose sight
of the van, all right?
And keep me updated on what you discover.
Yep. Will do.
I'll get something for you, sir.
Good work. That's all.
Is he here, my grandson?
Was he brought here?
Just let… let me see him, please?
Can you do that?
So, uh, he can't see anyone for now.
He's innocent.
He didn't do it.
My Jong-hyeok isn't that kind of person.
Captain, you know that.
Yes, I, uh…
Two cars and a motorcycle
are trailing us, sir.
Then floor it.
Huh?
Ho-jae.
How much do you like him?
What makes you think
I'll tell you anything?
Well, I like him a lot.
I know about his history with Lady Maeda.
So I understood
why he was so furious toward Jeonseung.
Last year, when he said
he was going
to destroy all the laboratories…
I knew without a doubt…
that I'd be on his side till the end.
At the time, I…
really believed
I could lay my life down for him.
However…
that didn't happen.
I didn't show up for him.
I never told him why.
Say that one more time.
"I'd give my life for Master Jang"?
Is that what I heard you say?
He's the first person
ever to acknowledge me.
He said that it was
okay to be myself.
He helped me realize
that I am human as well.
For the first time in my life…
it wasn't painful to be alive.
I have also
acknowledged you too.
I took you as my son, even though
you were born from a lowly courtesan.
I bestowed upon you
the prestige of my family name.
And yet,
this betrayal.
I'm sorry, Mother.
Let me go to Ho-jae.
Lift your head.
I said lift your head up.
Now.
The Najin inside you
will be in a deep sleep for 24 hours.
It will not be able
to protect you anymore.
If you are struck with a knife,
the wound will not heal.
If you are shot with a gun,
you will bleed and die from your wound.
Without the Najin, your body tissues…
can no longer regenerate
from a fatal wound.
Now you may be dismissed.
Perhaps now you'll learn
how weak and agonizing
the human body really is.
And how meaningless the justice of man is,
especially in the face of death.
The choice is yours to make.
I'll leave the door open.
To tell you the truth,
I was there that day a year ago.
But… there was no way for me to help him.
I was scared
that I might die.
There's no shame…
in being scared, you know?
There are those who are afraid of dying…
but there are also those
who are afraid to live.
Each person experiences fear uniquely.
From what I know,
Master Jang never questioned your loyalty.
So that means he understands.
So don't feel bad about it.
You're vulnerable now.
The Najin will be dormant
for 24 hours.
So if you're stabbed with a knife
or shot point-blank with a gun…
you will die.
How could you? What'd you do to me?
I told you.
I have to do this.
Otherwise, I might die.
And so we meet again.
So indeed.
Has it been a year?
I am tired of you and this mess.
I've always been
quite persistent, remember?
You finally find the woman
you've been waiting for all this time.
Why bother showing your face here again?
You have a death wish?
Don't worry about it.
Once I'm done with you,
I'll get back to living my life, okay?
Don't tell me you still trust Seung-jo.
Yeah.
Of course.
That poor girl, then.
Let's get this over with.
They lured Jang Tae-sang away,
and Seung-jo is with Ms. Yoon Chae-ok.
Honey.
My love.
If I end up doing the surgery,
do you think I'll be able
to play the cello again?
Of course.
You'll play even better
than before your accident.
And when do you think
I'll be able to receive the transplant?
I'm still searching
for the best one for you.
After three to six months,
it learns most of the body mechanics,
so it shouldn't put a huge toll
on the body after the transplant.
And the success rate is higher than
when in a larval stage. Is that correct?
Yes, we've had no fatalities
with any mature Najin transplants.
We'll go with this one.
We'll implant it in three months.
Just wait three more months.
You'll be able to walk again soon.
Enjoy your meal.
♪ The day I saw the light ♪
♪ You came into my life ♪
♪ The black curtain started to lift ♪
♪ Things happen
That you've never seen before ♪
♪ Then I see the new feast of light ♪
♪ Begin for me ♪
♪ The Gradation in Light ♪
♪ Inside of my heart ♪
♪ Forgotten story, you and me ♪